[♪ upbeat music playing]
- Hey, man.
- Morimo, what's up?
[both grunting]
- [Morimo laughing]
- Hey!
- Morning.
- [YAMADA] It's-a Mini!
- What are you doing?
[MORIMO] Schoolin' this guy.
- Whoa. Cool.
- Yeah. See?
[smacks lips]
[yawning]
Hmm...
[groans]
[inhales deeply]
What's up, Tani?
Mmm-mmm, mmm-mmm.
How's it hangin'?
- Ugh! Creepy.
- [exclaims]
Eat a chainsaw!
[SONG] Move or I crush
your donut hair.
[SUZUKI] Ugh, I hate you!
Knock it off and get moving!
You're going to be late.
[SUZUKI] I'm outie.
[indistinct chatter]
Morning, Suzuki.
Azuma and Taira
walking together.
Dude! Shut up!
[SUZUKI] Watanabe.
Satou. Nabesato.
- Hi!
- Hey. 'Sup?
[SUZUKI] Good morning, Yamada.
Yo!
Uh, hey.
Good morning to ya, Tani.
Morning.
[giggling]
Oh, my God, why are you
screaming at him?
I'm saving the world
one "hi" at a time.
Look, I made my lashes
extra lashy.
- Hmm. Did you?
- [giggles, groans]
Why don't you just use falsies?
I generally prefer
rocking the real thing,
working with the eyelashes
my mama gave me
and all that jazz.
But mascara is risky AF.
If you sweat or cry or rub it,
you're DOA.
I'm still on an eternal quest
to find the perfect formula
for me.
But I'm fighting the good fight,
so whatevs.
Any thoughts, Tani?
I don't know anything
about makeup.
[laughs enthusiastically]
You're savage as ever, Tani.
I totally love it!
Why do you get such a kick
out of pestering Tani
about things
he clearly has no interest in?
Girl, chill.
[Suzuki giggles] I love the way
he shuts me down.
I can't help myself.
[giggling continues]
If you ever need help
picking mascara,
- come to me, okay?
- [TANI] I won't.
Another slam
of the verbal door!
He's ruthless.
Stop bothering the poor guy.
[giggles weakly]
Mmm...
I'm sorry, Tani.
I know I always end up
yapping your ear off,
but the truth is...
[dramatically] I'm desperately
in love with you.
[♪ opening theme song playing]
Hey, did you finish
your homework?
I only did the parts that
I thought I might get right.
Dude, do the whole thing.
[SUZUKI] Sitting in the seat
next to me is Tani.
To everybody else in our class,
he's just a cookie-cutter,
glasses-wearing,
quiet dude who always
keeps to himself.
But when he does speak,
he speaks his mind.
Here, she's going to
flag this part
if you don't fix it.
[YAMADA] Come on.
C's get degrees, my dude.
[SUZUKI] And he has
the same attitude
no matter who he's with.
Have the homework?
- Homework?
- Yeah. Thanks for grabbing them.
Thank you. Tani.
[SUZUKI] Like the last time
we changed seats.
Now run along to your new spot.
[hyperventilating]
I'm right next to him.
This is wild! What do I do?!
Holler if you need
a cup of sugar, neighbor.
[TANI] Likewise.
[SUZUKI] Front row seats.
Look at us.
Reading the blackboard from here
is harder than you'd think.
But I got you.
I'll read anything
you can't make out,
so don't break your neck.
I'll be okay.
[Suzuki giggles nervously]
Okie-dokie.
Tani doesn't change
who he is for anybody.
[SATOU] Live has more character.
[SUZUKI] I think
that's awesome.
I really admire him.
[WATANABE] Suzuki,
which do you prefer?
Sorry, I zoned out for a little.
Oh, my God.
[clears throat] In my opinion,
a real-life person
can rev up a crowd
way better than some
dumb recording ever could.
- Tell 'em, Tani!
- I have no clue.
Sorry about her.
She's certifiable.
If she's bothering you,
just let us know.
[Suzuki grunts]
I don't mind at all.
[gasps]
See? He says he doesn't mind.
Ohh! Oh, thank God!
I'm so sorry, Tani.
I love you,
and I want to talk
to you normally.
I'm just always in my head
about how people see me,
so I can't talk to you
in a way
that reveals my feelings.
I admire the crap
out of you, dude,
but you and I
are polar opposites.
Okay. After school,
let's go to KingBurg.
Hey. Dining with us, ding-dong?
Uh...
I need to do my homework.
[WATANABE] Hmm? Hmm?
Hmm? Hmm?
[SUZUKI] Vamonos
a la Burg!
[BOTH] Yay!
Hey, Suzuki.
- Can I copy your homework?
- Again?
- [YAMADA] Please save me.
- [groans]
You're hopeless. Here.
[YAMADA] Thank you!
Oh, Suzuki.
The story you posted
made me laugh out loud.
Aw, can I follow your account
so I can see it too?
[SUZUKI] I didn't post
anything weird, did I?
Of course, girly-swirly.
You go for it.
[YAMADA] Did you know?
Tani is, like, really smart.
[coughing]
He totally carried our group.
I've seen him shuffling off
to cram school.
[WATANABE] Think he's gunning
for UTokyo?
[TAIRA] How should I know?
[laughs awkwardly] That guy
has got serious promise.
I feel like he lives
in a different world
from the rest of us.
[SATOU] Do not
lump me in with you.
Out of everybody here,
Suzuki probably knows him
the best.
Oh, yeah? You really think so?
[slurps, coughs]
- Ew! Plague!
- Are you gonna make it?
[coughs, laughs] I'm A-okay.
I just gotta space out
my talking
- and my sipping better.
- Don't die on us.
Aw!
SudaKen just won
Most Beloved Actor
for the second time.
[laughs] You chicks always go
for the bad boys.
No, doy! SudaKen is, like,
beyond boyfriend material.
[WATANABE] You're always
the ultimate SudaKen stan.
[cackling]
They say reading the room
is to protect
other people's feelings.
But in my case...
I totally do it
to protect my own.
And yet...
all I feel is exhausted.
Why is that?
- [GROUP] Fight! Win!
- [BOY 1] Go! Fight! Win!
[sighs]
[BOY 1] Go! Fight! Fight! Win!
[SUZUKI] I should head home.
[door closes]
[yawning loudly]
[exclaims]
Oh, hey, Tani. It's pretty late.
Why are you doing here?
My face probably
looked hideous just now.
I needed to turn in
my committee work.
Not to be weird, but which way
do you walk home?
I take a right at the gate.
Same here!
Okay. No one's watching.
[hesitates] Hey, Tani.
Oh, don't do it.
Would you mind
if I walked along with you?
Oh, you did it!
Oh, God, I'm gonna puke!
It is madness
we live in the same direction.
Strange we've never
run into each other before.
[TANI] Mmm.
Doy!
I'm always running around
goofing off after school.
Of course I don't see you.
And you stay busy with
the student council
stuff, right?
[TANI] Right.
Oh!
We decided to swing by
KingBurg the other day,
and they gave me a burger.
It was so flippin' big,
it was sliding off the bun.
It was more like I ordered meat
with bun on the side.
I had no idea how to eat it
without looking like a weirdo.
Is this interesting at all?
[TANI] Was it good?
Oh, yeah. Like, crazy good.
Loved it!
You know, if you want to,
we could go grab one together.
JK!
Okay.
Huh?
Did he just say yes?
Is he being polite?
Matching my vibe?
No way.
Tani isn't
that kind of person.
[groans softly]
I've gotta think.
Think, girl. Your window
to reply is closing!
- It's no use.
- [heart pounding]
My heart is pounding
way too hard!
I can't do it!
[squeals] Oh, um, I'm sorry!
[giggling nervously]
[♪ dreamy music playing]
[gasps]
It can't be.
Am I...
dreaming right now?
Is this real life?
He's holding my hand.
My sweaty, sweaty hand.
And my heart is pounding
in my ears.
Like, really pounding.
Like, what if I die?
[GIRL 1] Did you catch that?
He was seriously on one today.
[GIRL 2] And he thought
he was being chill!
[GIRL 1] It's sad.
Some people just have
zero social awareness.
[SUZUKI] After that is a blur.
I THINK WE PROBABLY SAID
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
I have no idea how I got home.
[Song humming]
I'm ho-- [screams]
You have a bedroom, you freak!
Right.
Forgot.
[gasps, screams]
[SONG] Good Lord.
[SUZUKI] We... held hands.
[SUZUKI'S MOTHER]
Aren't you going to eat?
If you're not,
then I'll help you.
[SUZUKI] Not only that.
He started it!
That was crazy. And he's crazy.
And I'm going crazy.
How the flip am I supposed
to go to school
and act like a human being?!
I'm never gonna go to sleep.
My heart is trying to beat
through my chest !
[screams]
[SONG] Shut up!
[birds chirping]
[weakly] I need to get bumpers.
The heck it so bright for?
Can't be morning already.
Huh?
[gasps]
[screaming]
I haven't been absent
or tardy all year!
Hello? Family?!
Come on, Mom!
Late is one thing,
but it's practically midday!
Well, guess there's no point
rushing now.
Come here.
It's lunchtime,
but good morning!
[SATOU] You're never this late.
Yeesh. You should have
taken the day off.
I know, but I didn't want
to miss P.E.
Okay, weirdo.
Look who finally showed.
[SUZUKI] At long last.
Hey, so I've got
a question for you.
Are you and Tani,
like, a thing now?
Huh?
Yeah. Gapacho said he saw you
walking home together,
so I thought I should ask.
[SUZUKI] Who the eff
is Gapacho?
That's not a real person.
[YAMADA] Gapacho is real,
and he knows what he saw.
- Sure thing, dude.
- [SUZUKI] Whoa!
Slow your freaking roll
there, Yamada!
Right now, Tani and I are in
the might-be-mutual,
but-not-yet-confirmed phase
of liking each other.
The most delicate, fragile,
super freaking important
phase of all.
It's not something
you could just poke fun at,
you big rube!
I am playing for keeps here!
Also... what?
- Somebody saw us?
- Hello?
[SUZUKI] Saw us where?
[laughing awkwardly] I, uh...
[quivering]
It's not like that, dude!
Excuse me.
Hey, that's my seat.
[groans]
I need my notebook.
[YAMADA] Oops.
Sorry, man. I'll move.
It's fine.
- The period's over.
- Oh.
[Suzuki whimpers]
Oh.
That could not have been worse.
[TEACHER] Our main source
of energy is carbohydrates.
[SUZUKI] He heard me denying
anything between us
like I was accused of a felony!
I was crazy rude.
[exclaims] You've got it wrong!
I didn't mean for it
to come out like that!
I'm sorry, Tani, I...
No, no!
I literally could never.
But I need to apologize
ASAGDMFP!
What do I do?
I hope I didn't hurt
Tani's feelings.
I hate this.
It's so over for me.
[WATANABE] Suzuki!
You're supposed to be
picking up the shuttes!
[SATOU] With your hands.
[SUZUKI] Why can't I ever do
anything right?
[GIRL 3] Sorry, Suzuki.
[bell ringing melodically]
Talk, I have to talk.
The longer I wait,
the worse it gets.
But... here?
Here, where there are people
who can perceive me?
[breathing shakily]
- Suzuki.
- [screaming]
Oh. Hey, Tani.
About yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Forget it happened.
Huh?
If we don't use this
epic popcorn coupon today,
it's gonna expire!
I saw you chatting it up
with Tani just now.
The jig is up, girl.
- Hmm?
- Are you okay?
- [both laughing]
- No way.
[laughing] Wait wait, wait.
Don't tell me.
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter fades away]
With Tani...
it's more than friendship.
- I love him.
- [ALL] Hmm?
[SUZUKI]
But I ruined everything.
Huh?
[SUZUKI] Yesterday,
I worked up the courage to ask
if we could walk home together
and now I...
drove him away!
What am I supposed to do?
Huh?
No!
What?! Why didn't you tell me?!
All this time,
I thought you guys
were regular
walking home together.
I didn't know you were
walking home, like, together!
Oh... Oh, my God.
I made fun of you about this.
I'm a horrible person.
Dude. We know. Shut up.
So is it bad
that Tani already left?
[exclaims] Very bad.
You might catch him if you run.
Gotta fight for love!
Get your man!
[SUZUKI] I'm goin'!
Don't worry about the popcorn.
We'll eat it without you.
[SUZUKI] That's fine,
I don't care.
Noice!
[YAMADA] Go, Suzuki!
You better not put
your name to shame!
[WATANABE] Rev that engine,
car girl!
- [engine revving]
- [yelling]
SLOW SLOW SLOW
Oh. She's slow.
[Suzuki panting]
Keep trying, girl!
- Push it! Let's go!
- Faster.
[SUZUKI] I'm in shock.
[screaming]
Saying how I feel out loud
has been this easy
the whole time?
[TANI] I gave in to temptation.
That's the whole story.
She always talks to me
at school,
but that's just banter.
She doesn't care
about me personally.
I just happen to sit
next to her in class.
Would you mind if
I walked along with you?
[TANI] Or that's what
I used to believe.
[sighs]
[Suzuki panting]
[TANI] Today, I thought
she might not come to school.
It's not like that, dude!
[TANI] It felt strange.
I've gotten so used
to Suzuki talking to me.
[panting]
[TANI] A day without her...
[SUZUKI] Tani!
...is just too quiet.
I...
love you!
[Suzuki panting heavily]
I... I'm sorry
for always talking
about stupid stuff
to get your attention.
I'm sorry for what I said
in class.
I really didn't mean it
like that.
I just...
I didn't know
how to talk to you, Tani,
and I was afraid of
what everyone would think
if they found out how I felt.
I am so beyond totally lame.
But I...
I want to spend
more time with you,
more than anything in the world.
And I was so happy
when you held my hand,
I thought I was dreaming.
I couldn't sleep,
that's why I ended up
being so late for school.
I mean, I did sleep,
but at the wrong times.
[TANI] Hmm...
Hey, Suzuki.
- Uh-huh?
- Listen...
When you're not talking,
I don't know what to say.
I'm not good with conversation.
I guess that's how
beyond totally lame I am.
Is that okay with you?
[gasps]
That face you're making
is so adorable!
[TANI] Whoa, there.
What do you want me to say?
Isn't it obvious by now?!
[wailing]
Sorry. I feel like
I made you cry.
Well, yeah.
You kind of did, so...
- [TANI] Uh...
- [SUZUKI] Huh?
Right. You're wearing mascara.
I shouldn't rub it.
[exclaims]
You really listening to me
all this time, weren't you?!
No way!
- My heart is all fluttery!
- Huh? Fluttery?
Are you okay?
[screams]
[♪ closing theme song playing]